<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Room requirements -->
  <NeedThroneAssigned>Need throneroom</NeedThroneAssigned>
  <NeedThroneAssignedDesc>One of your people has a royal title that requires a throneroom, but no throneroom is assigned.\n\nBuild a throne in a room, then assign the throne to the title holder. The throneroom should be appropriately sized and decorated to satisfy the title's specific requirements.</NeedThroneAssignedDesc>

  <UndignifiedBedroom>Undignified bedroom</UndignifiedBedroom>
  <UndignifiedBedroomDesc>One of your people has a royal title that requires a bedroom with specific features. Either no bedroom is assigned, or the assigned bedroom doesn't satisfy the requirements.</UndignifiedBedroomDesc>

  <NeedBedroomAssigned>Title requires bedroom</NeedBedroomAssigned>
  <NeedBedroomAssignedDesc>One of your people has a royal title that requires a personal bedroom, but no bedroom is assigned.\n\nAssign them a personal bedroom. The bedroom should be appropriately sized and decorated to satisfy the title's specific requirements.</NeedBedroomAssignedDesc>

  <UndignifiedThroneroom>Undignified throneroom</UndignifiedThroneroom>
  <UndignifiedThroneroomDesc>One of your people has a royal title and a throne, but the throne room does not satisfy the title's requirements.</UndignifiedThroneroomDesc>
  
  <RoyalNoAcceptableFood>No acceptable food</RoyalNoAcceptableFood>
  <RoyalNoAcceptableFoodDesc>One of your people has a royal title with specific food requirements. But there's no food available that satisfies these requirements.</RoyalNoAcceptableFoodDesc>

  <RoomRequirementGracePeriodDesc>{0} days until requirement begins</RoomRequirementGracePeriodDesc>

  <ThroneroomInvalidConfiguration>Throne not usable</ThroneroomInvalidConfiguration>
  <ThroneroomInvalidConfigurationDesc>A throne is not usable because of how it is set up:</ThroneroomInvalidConfigurationDesc>
  
  <MonumentMarkerMissingBlueprints>Monument missing blueprints</MonumentMarkerMissingBlueprints>
  <MonumentMarkerMissingBlueprintsDesc>The monument won't be completed because blueprints have not been placed for all its parts.\n\nSelect the monument marker and click "Place blueprints", or place the blueprints manually.</MonumentMarkerMissingBlueprintsDesc>

</LanguageData>